<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-12-11T18:21:43-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Dr.Google ?</title><subtitle>Describe your website here.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Motivation</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/motivation/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Motivation" /><published>2018-12-10T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-10T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/motivation</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/motivation/">&lt;html&gt;
&lt;head&gt;
&lt;meta name=&quot;viewport&quot; content=&quot;width=device-width, initial-scale=1&quot; /&gt;
&lt;style&gt;
* {box-sizing: border-box}
body {font-family: Verdana, sans-serif; margin:0}
.mySlides {display: none}
img {vertical-align: middle;}

/* Slideshow container */
.slideshow-container {
  max-width: 1000px;
  position: relative;
  margin: auto;
}

/* Next &amp; previous buttons */
.prev, .next {
  cursor: pointer;
  position: absolute;
  top: 50%;
  width: auto;
  padding: 16px;
  margin-top: -22px;
  color: white;
  font-weight: bold;
  font-size: 18px;
  transition: 0.6s ease;
  border-radius: 0 3px 3px 0;
  user-select: none;
}

/* Position the &quot;next button&quot; to the right */
.next {
  right: 0;
  border-radius: 3px 0 0 3px;
}

/* On hover, add a black background color with a little bit see-through */
.prev:hover, .next:hover {
  background-color: rgba(0,0,0,0.8);
}

/* Caption text */
.text {
  color: #f2f2f2;
  font-size: 15px;
  padding: 8px 12px;
  position: absolute;
  bottom: 8px;
  width: 100%;
  text-align: center;
}

/* Number text (1/3 etc) */
.numbertext {
  color: #f2f2f2;
  font-size: 12px;
  padding: 8px 12px;
  position: absolute;
  top: 0;
}

/* The dots/bullets/indicators */
.dot {
  cursor: pointer;
  height: 15px;
  width: 15px;
  margin: 0 2px;
  background-color: #bbb;
  border-radius: 50%;
  display: inline-block;
  transition: background-color 0.6s ease;
}

.active, .dot:hover {
  background-color: #717171;
}

/* Fading animation */
.fade {
  -webkit-animation-name: fade;
  -webkit-animation-duration: 1.5s;
  animation-name: fade;
  animation-duration: 1.5s;
}

@-webkit-keyframes fade {
  from {opacity: .4} 
  to {opacity: 1}
}

@keyframes fade {
  from {opacity: .4} 
  to {opacity: 1}
}

/* On smaller screens, decrease text size */
@media only screen and (max-width: 300px) {
  .prev, .next,.text {font-size: 11px}
}
&lt;/style&gt;
&lt;/head&gt;
&lt;body&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;slideshow-container&quot;&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;mySlides fade&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;numbertext&quot;&gt;1 / 3&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/slides/my-pics1/pic1.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Caption Text&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;mySlides fade&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;numbertext&quot;&gt;2 / 3&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/slides/my-pics1/pic2.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Caption Two&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;mySlides fade&quot;&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;numbertext&quot;&gt;3 / 3&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/slides/my-pics1/pic3.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width:100%&quot; /&gt;
  &lt;div class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Caption Three&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;a class=&quot;prev&quot; onclick=&quot;plusSlides(-1)&quot;&gt;&amp;#10094;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a class=&quot;next&quot; onclick=&quot;plusSlides(1)&quot;&gt;&amp;#10095;&lt;/a&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;

&lt;div style=&quot;text-align:center&quot;&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;dot&quot; onclick=&quot;currentSlide(1)&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
  &lt;span class=&quot;dot&quot; onclick=&quot;currentSlide(2)&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
  &lt;span class=&quot;dot&quot; onclick=&quot;currentSlide(3)&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;script&gt;
var slideIndex = 1;
showSlides(slideIndex);

function plusSlides(n) {
  showSlides(slideIndex += n);
}

function currentSlide(n) {
  showSlides(slideIndex = n);
}

function showSlides(n) {
  var i;
  var slides = document.getElementsByClassName(&quot;mySlides&quot;);
  var dots = document.getElementsByClassName(&quot;dot&quot;);
  if (n &gt; slides.length) {slideIndex = 1}    
  if (n &lt; 1) {slideIndex = slides.length}
  for (i = 0; i &lt; slides.length; i++) {
      slides[i].style.display = &quot;none&quot;;  
  }
  for (i = 0; i &lt; dots.length; i++) {
      dots[i].className = dots[i].className.replace(&quot; active&quot;, &quot;&quot;);
  }
  slides[slideIndex-1].style.display = &quot;block&quot;;  
  dots[slideIndex-1].className += &quot; active&quot;;
}
&lt;/script&gt;

&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What would you do when you’ve been having this weird headache intermittently for a week? Would you directly go to a doctor? Guess the answer is the same for most of us: we google it first!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This brings us to wonder what google health search trends are telling us. Are people generally becoming more aware of health conditions and health risks? How does search interest for top health issues change over time? Are there huge differences in heath concerns between states?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We believe google searches offer much more information than symptom description or  illness diagnose. Thus, we decided to take a further look into the search numbers.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample post" /><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/%7B%22background%22=%3E%22triangular.png%22%7D" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Objectives</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/objective/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Objectives" /><published>2018-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/objective</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/objective/">&lt;p&gt;Through this project, we want to answer the following questions:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Are people more concerned about health now? Is the trend the same across states?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Are people in different states concerned about different diseases?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Is there an association between search interest and actual disease prevalence?
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Can a year’s search interest predict a relevant health outcome in the following year?&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Are states who care more about health actually healthier or more vulnerable?&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;What can be inferred and what suggestions can be drawn for public healthcare provider, policy maker, and friends moving to the U.S.?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample post" /><category term="code" /><category term="highlighting" /><summary type="html">Through this project, we want to answer the following questions: Are people more concerned about health now? Is the trend the same across states?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Data Sets</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/datasets/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Data Sets" /><published>2018-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-09T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/datasets</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/datasets/">&lt;p&gt;We found and synergized two data sources.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.kaggle.com/GoogleNewsLab/health-searches-us-county/home&quot;&gt;Google Health Search Interest Data: &lt;/a&gt;
The data consist of regional interest by condition over time. There is information on metropolitan areas in 46 States, 9 Search topics: cancer, cardiovascular, stroke, depression, rehab, vaccine, diarrhea, obesity, diabetes, and 14 years (2004-2017).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://chronicdata.cdc.gov/Behavioral-Risk-Factors/Behavioral-Risk-Factor-Surveillance-System-BRFSS-P/dttw-5yxu&quot;&gt;CDC Selected Metropolitan Area Risk Trends (SMART) Data &lt;/a&gt;
The source has information on disease prevalence in the U.S. from 2011 to present.
We tidy data from this source to get prevalence by year, state, and disease and apply them into the association analysis with search data from the former source.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample post" /><category term="link post" /><summary type="html">We found and synergized two data sources.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Methods</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/methods/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Methods" /><published>2018-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2018-12-08T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/methods</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/methods/">&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tidy the data from wide version into long version.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Draw line charts to present all disease searches by state and year.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Draw distribution maps for each disease to see the differences in search preference between states. (The search data reflects the relative search interest for people in a certain area.)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Present distribution maps for the actual disease prevalences across the country. Compare prevalence with the search interest to see if the states who care more about health are also healthier.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Conduct regression analysis for each disease to see if more search is associated with higher or lower prevalence, and if the association differ between diseases?&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Most importantly, analyze the feasibility to conduct inference and suggestions for public healthcare provider, policy maker, and friends moving to the U.S. (e.g. vaccine amount prediction, public education on reducing obesity.)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample post" /><category term="video" /><summary type="html">Tidy the data from wide version into long version. Draw line charts to present all disease searches by state and year. Draw distribution maps for each disease to see the differences in search preference between states. (The search data reflects the relative search interest for people in a certain area.) Present distribution maps for the actual disease prevalences across the country. Compare prevalence with the search interest to see if the states who care more about health are also healthier. Conduct regression analysis for each disease to see if more search is associated with higher or lower prevalence, and if the association differ between diseases?</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Post with Large Feature Image and Text</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/readability-feature-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Post with Large Feature Image and Text" /><published>2013-05-23T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2013-05-23T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/readability-feature-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/readability-feature-post/">&lt;p&gt;This is a sample post with a large feature image up top and tons of text. Odio ad blue bottle vinyl, 90’s narwhal commodo bitters pour-over nostrud. Ugh est hashtag in, fingerstache adipisicing laboris esse Pinterest shabby chic Portland. Shoreditch bicycle rights anim, flexitarian laboris put a bird on it vinyl cupidatat narwhal. Hashtag artisan skateboard, flannel Bushwick nesciunt salvia aute fixie do plaid post-ironic dolor McSweeney’s. Cliche pour-over chambray nulla four loko skateboard sapiente hashtag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vero laborum commodo occupy. Semiotics voluptate mumblecore pug. Cosby sweater ullamco quinoa ennui assumenda, sapiente occupy delectus lo-fi. Ea fashion axe Marfa cillum aliquip. Retro Bushwick keytar cliche. Before they sold out sustainable gastropub Marfa readymade, ethical Williamsburg skateboard brunch qui consectetur gentrify semiotics. Mustache cillum irony, fingerstache magna pour-over keffiyeh tousled selfies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;cupidatat-90s-lo-fi-authentic-try-hard&quot;&gt;Cupidatat 90’s lo-fi authentic try-hard&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In pug Portland incididunt mlkshk put a bird on it vinyl quinoa. Terry Richardson shabby chic +1, scenester Tonx excepteur tempor fugiat voluptate fingerstache aliquip nisi next level. Farm-to-table hashtag Truffaut, Odd Future ex meggings gentrify single-origin coffee try-hard 90’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sartorial hoodie&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Labore viral forage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tote bag selvage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;DIY exercitation et id ugh tumblr church-key&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Incididunt umami sriracha, ethical fugiat VHS ex assumenda yr irure direct trade. Marfa Truffaut bicycle rights, kitsch placeat Etsy kogi asymmetrical. Beard locavore flexitarian, kitsch photo booth hoodie plaid ethical readymade leggings yr.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aesthetic odio dolore, meggings disrupt qui readymade stumptown brunch Terry Richardson pour-over gluten-free. Banksy american apparel in selfies, biodiesel flexitarian organic meh wolf quinoa gentrify banjo kogi. Readymade tofu ex, scenester dolor umami fingerstache occaecat fashion axe Carles jean shorts minim. Keffiyeh fashion axe nisi Godard mlkshk dolore. Lomo you probably haven’t heard of them eu non, Odd Future Truffaut pug keytar meggings McSweeney’s Pinterest cred. Etsy literally aute esse, eu bicycle rights qui meggings fanny pack. Gentrify leggings pug flannel duis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;forage-occaecat-cardigan-qui&quot;&gt;Forage occaecat cardigan qui&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fashion axe hella gastropub lo-fi kogi 90’s aliquip +1 veniam delectus tousled. Cred sriracha locavore gastropub kale chips, iPhone mollit sartorial. Anim dolore 8-bit, pork belly dolor photo booth aute flannel small batch. Dolor disrupt ennui, tattooed whatever salvia Banksy sartorial roof party selfies raw denim sint meh pour-over. Ennui eu cardigan sint, gentrify iPhone cornhole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Whatever velit occaecat quis deserunt gastropub, leggings elit tousled roof party 3 wolf moon kogi pug blue bottle ea. Fashion axe shabby chic Austin quinoa pickled laborum bitters next level, disrupt deep v accusamus non fingerstache.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tote bag asymmetrical elit sunt. Occaecat authentic Marfa, hella McSweeney’s next level irure veniam master cleanse. Sed hoodie letterpress artisan wolf leggings, 3 wolf moon commodo ullamco. Anim occupy ea labore Terry Richardson. Tofu ex master cleanse in whatever pitchfork banh mi, occupy fugiat fanny pack Austin authentic. Magna fugiat 3 wolf moon, labore McSweeney’s sustainable vero consectetur. Gluten-free disrupt enim, aesthetic fugiat jean shorts trust fund keffiyeh magna try-hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hoodie-duis&quot;&gt;Hoodie Duis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually salvia consectetur, hoodie duis lomo YOLO sunt sriracha. Aute pop-up brunch farm-to-table odio, salvia irure occaecat. Sriracha small batch literally skateboard. Echo Park nihil hoodie, aliquip forage artisan laboris. Trust fund reprehenderit nulla locavore. Stumptown raw denim kitsch, keffiyeh nulla twee dreamcatcher fanny pack ullamco 90’s pop-up est culpa farm-to-table. Selfies 8-bit do pug odio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;thundercats-ho&quot;&gt;Thundercats Ho!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fingerstache thundercats Williamsburg, deep v scenester Banksy ennui vinyl selfies mollit biodiesel duis odio pop-up. Banksy 3 wolf moon try-hard, sapiente enim stumptown deep v ad letterpress. Squid beard brunch, exercitation raw denim yr sint direct trade. Raw denim narwhal id, flannel DIY McSweeney’s seitan. Letterpress artisan bespoke accusamus, meggings laboris consequat Truffaut qui in seitan. Sustainable cornhole Schlitz, twee Cosby sweater banh mi deep v forage letterpress flannel whatever keffiyeh. Sartorial cred irure, semiotics ethical sed blue bottle nihil letterpress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Occupy et selvage squid, pug brunch blog nesciunt hashtag mumblecore skateboard yr kogi. Ugh small batch swag four loko. Fap post-ironic qui tote bag farm-to-table american apparel scenester keffiyeh vero, swag non pour-over gentrify authentic pitchfork. Schlitz scenester lo-fi voluptate, tote bag irony bicycle rights pariatur vero Vice freegan wayfarers exercitation nisi shoreditch. Chambray tofu vero sed. Street art swag literally leggings, Cosby sweater mixtape PBR lomo Banksy non in pitchfork ennui McSweeney’s selfies. Odd Future Banksy non authentic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aliquip enim artisan dolor post-ironic. Pug tote bag Marfa, deserunt pour-over Portland wolf eu odio intelligentsia american apparel ugh ea. Sunt viral et, 3 wolf moon gastropub pug id. Id fashion axe est typewriter, mlkshk Portland art party aute brunch. Sint pork belly Cosby sweater, deep v mumblecore kitsch american apparel. Try-hard direct trade tumblr sint skateboard. Adipisicing bitters excepteur biodiesel, pickled gastropub aute veniam.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample post" /><category term="readability" /><summary type="html">This is a sample post with a large feature image up top and tons of text. Odio ad blue bottle vinyl, 90’s narwhal commodo bitters pour-over nostrud. Ugh est hashtag in, fingerstache adipisicing laboris esse Pinterest shabby chic Portland. Shoreditch bicycle rights anim, flexitarian laboris put a bird on it vinyl cupidatat narwhal. Hashtag artisan skateboard, flannel Bushwick nesciunt salvia aute fixie do plaid post-ironic dolor McSweeney’s. Cliche pour-over chambray nulla four loko skateboard sapiente hashtag.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/abstract-7.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">A Post with Images</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/sample-post-images/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Post with Images" /><published>2013-05-22T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2013-05-22T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sample-post-images</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/sample-post-images/">&lt;p&gt;Here are some examples of what a post with images might look like. If you want to display two or three images next to each other responsively use &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;figure&lt;/code&gt; with the appropriate &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;class&lt;/code&gt;. Each instance of &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;figure&lt;/code&gt; is auto-numbered and displayed in the caption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;figures-for-images-or-video&quot;&gt;Figures (for images or video)&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;one-up&quot;&gt;One Up&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;figure&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8426/7758832526_cc8f681e48_b.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://farm9.staticflickr.com/8426/7758832526_cc8f681e48_c.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;figcaption&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/80901381@N04/7758832526/&quot; title=&quot;Morning Fog Emerging From Trees by A Guy Taking Pictures, on Flickr&quot;&gt;Morning Fog Emerging From Trees by A Guy Taking Pictures, on Flickr&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;two-up&quot;&gt;Two Up&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apply the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;half&lt;/code&gt; class like so to display two images side by side that share the same caption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-html highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;figure&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;class=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;half&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;img&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;src=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;/images/image-filename-1.jpg&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;alt=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;img&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;src=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;/images/image-filename-2.jpg&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;alt=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Caption describing these two images.&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And you’ll get something that looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half&quot;&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;http://placehold.it/1200x600.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;http://placehold.it/1200x600.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Two images.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;three-up&quot;&gt;Three Up&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apply the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;third&lt;/code&gt; class like so to display three images side by side that share the same caption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-html highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;figure&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;class=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;third&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;href=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;http://placehold.it/1200x600.jpg&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;img&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;src=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;alt=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;href=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;http://placehold.it/1200x600.jpg&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;img&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;src=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;alt=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;href=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;http://placehold.it/1200x600.jpg&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;img&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;src=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;alt=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
	&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;figcaption&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Caption describing these three images.&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/figcaption&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/figure&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And you’ll get something that looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;third&quot;&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;http://placehold.it/1200x600.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;http://placehold.it/1200x600.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;http://placehold.it/1200x600.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;http://placehold.it/1200x600.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;http://placehold.it/1200x600.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;a href=&quot;http://placehold.it/1200x600.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://placehold.it/600x300.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
	&lt;figcaption&gt;Three images.&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;alternative-way&quot;&gt;Alternative way&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another way to achieve the same result is to include &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;gallery&lt;/code&gt; Liquid template. In this case you
don’t have to write any HTML tags – just copy a small block of code, adjust the parameters (see below)
and fill the block with any number of links to images. You can mix relative and external links.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the block you might want to use:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-liquid highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;capture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;%}&lt;/span&gt;
	/images/abstract-10.jpg
	/images/abstract-11.jpg
	http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/2/24/Lenna.png
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;endcapture&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;%}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;include&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;gallery&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nv&quot;&gt;images&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;caption&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Test images&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;cols&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;mi&quot;&gt;3&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;%}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Parameters:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;caption&lt;/code&gt;: Sets the caption under the gallery (see &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;figcaption&lt;/code&gt; HTML tag above);&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;cols&lt;/code&gt;: Sets the number of columns of the gallery.
Available values: [1..3].&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It will look something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;third&quot;&gt;
    
    &lt;a href=&quot;/images/abstract-10.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/abstract-10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    
    &lt;a href=&quot;/images/abstract-11.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/abstract-11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    
    &lt;a href=&quot;http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/2/24/Lenna.png&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/2/24/Lenna.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
    
    &lt;figcaption&gt;Test images&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample post" /><category term="images" /><category term="test" /><summary type="html">Here are some examples of what a post with images might look like. If you want to display two or three images next to each other responsively use figure with the appropriate class. Each instance of figure is auto-numbered and displayed in the caption.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Testing Readability with a Bunch of Text</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/readability-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Testing Readability with a Bunch of Text" /><published>2012-05-22T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2012-05-22T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/readability-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/readability-post/">&lt;p&gt;Portland in shoreditch Vice, labore typewriter pariatur hoodie fap sartorial Austin. Pinterest literally occupy Schlitz forage. Odio ad blue bottle vinyl, 90’s narwhal commodo bitters pour-over nostrud. Ugh est hashtag in, fingerstache adipisicing laboris esse Pinterest shabby chic Portland. Shoreditch bicycle rights anim, flexitarian laboris put a bird on it vinyl cupidatat narwhal. Hashtag artisan skateboard, flannel Bushwick nesciunt salvia aute fixie do plaid post-ironic dolor McSweeney’s. Cliche pour-over chambray nulla four loko skateboard sapiente hashtag.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vero laborum commodo occupy. Semiotics voluptate mumblecore pug. Cosby sweater ullamco quinoa ennui assumenda, sapiente occupy delectus lo-fi. Ea fashion axe Marfa cillum aliquip. Retro Bushwick keytar cliche. Before they sold out sustainable gastropub Marfa readymade, ethical Williamsburg skateboard brunch qui consectetur gentrify semiotics. Mustache cillum irony, fingerstache magna pour-over keffiyeh tousled selfies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;cupidatat-90s-lo-fi-authentic-try-hard&quot;&gt;Cupidatat 90’s lo-fi authentic try-hard&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In pug Portland incididunt mlkshk put a bird on it vinyl quinoa. Terry Richardson shabby chic +1, scenester Tonx excepteur tempor fugiat voluptate fingerstache aliquip nisi next level. Farm-to-table hashtag Truffaut, Odd Future ex meggings gentrify single-origin coffee try-hard 90’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sartorial hoodie&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Labore viral forage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Tote bag selvage&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;DIY exercitation et id ugh tumblr church-key&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Incididunt umami sriracha, ethical fugiat VHS ex assumenda yr irure direct trade. Marfa Truffaut bicycle rights, kitsch placeat Etsy kogi asymmetrical. Beard locavore flexitarian, kitsch photo booth hoodie plaid ethical readymade leggings yr.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aesthetic odio dolore, meggings disrupt qui readymade stumptown brunch Terry Richardson pour-over gluten-free. Banksy american apparel in selfies, biodiesel flexitarian organic meh wolf quinoa gentrify banjo kogi. Readymade tofu ex, scenester dolor umami fingerstache occaecat fashion axe Carles jean shorts minim. Keffiyeh fashion axe nisi Godard mlkshk dolore. Lomo you probably haven’t heard of them eu non, Odd Future Truffaut pug keytar meggings McSweeney’s Pinterest cred. Etsy literally aute esse, eu bicycle rights qui meggings fanny pack. Gentrify leggings pug flannel duis.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;forage-occaecat-cardigan-qui&quot;&gt;Forage occaecat cardigan qui&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fashion axe hella gastropub lo-fi kogi 90’s aliquip +1 veniam delectus tousled. Cred sriracha locavore gastropub kale chips, iPhone mollit sartorial. Anim dolore 8-bit, pork belly dolor photo booth aute flannel small batch. Dolor disrupt ennui, tattooed whatever salvia Banksy sartorial roof party selfies raw denim sint meh pour-over. Ennui eu cardigan sint, gentrify iPhone cornhole.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Whatever velit occaecat quis deserunt gastropub, leggings elit tousled roof party 3 wolf moon kogi pug blue bottle ea. Fashion axe shabby chic Austin quinoa pickled laborum bitters next level, disrupt deep v accusamus non fingerstache.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tote bag asymmetrical elit sunt. Occaecat authentic Marfa, hella McSweeney’s next level irure veniam master cleanse. Sed hoodie letterpress artisan wolf leggings, 3 wolf moon commodo ullamco. Anim occupy ea labore Terry Richardson. Tofu ex master cleanse in whatever pitchfork banh mi, occupy fugiat fanny pack Austin authentic. Magna fugiat 3 wolf moon, labore McSweeney’s sustainable vero consectetur. Gluten-free disrupt enim, aesthetic fugiat jean shorts trust fund keffiyeh magna try-hard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;hoodie-duis&quot;&gt;Hoodie Duis&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Actually salvia consectetur, hoodie duis lomo YOLO sunt sriracha. Aute pop-up brunch farm-to-table odio, salvia irure occaecat. Sriracha small batch literally skateboard. Echo Park nihil hoodie, aliquip forage artisan laboris. Trust fund reprehenderit nulla locavore. Stumptown raw denim kitsch, keffiyeh nulla twee dreamcatcher fanny pack ullamco 90’s pop-up est culpa farm-to-table. Selfies 8-bit do pug odio.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;thundercats-ho&quot;&gt;Thundercats Ho!&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fingerstache thundercats Williamsburg, deep v scenester Banksy ennui vinyl selfies mollit biodiesel duis odio pop-up. Banksy 3 wolf moon try-hard, sapiente enim stumptown deep v ad letterpress. Squid beard brunch, exercitation raw denim yr sint direct trade. Raw denim narwhal id, flannel DIY McSweeney’s seitan. Letterpress artisan bespoke accusamus, meggings laboris consequat Truffaut qui in seitan. Sustainable cornhole Schlitz, twee Cosby sweater banh mi deep v forage letterpress flannel whatever keffiyeh. Sartorial cred irure, semiotics ethical sed blue bottle nihil letterpress.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Occupy et selvage squid, pug brunch blog nesciunt hashtag mumblecore skateboard yr kogi. Ugh small batch swag four loko. Fap post-ironic qui tote bag farm-to-table american apparel scenester keffiyeh vero, swag non pour-over gentrify authentic pitchfork. Schlitz scenester lo-fi voluptate, tote bag irony bicycle rights pariatur vero Vice freegan wayfarers exercitation nisi shoreditch. Chambray tofu vero sed. Street art swag literally leggings, Cosby sweater mixtape PBR lomo Banksy non in pitchfork ennui McSweeney’s selfies. Odd Future Banksy non authentic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aliquip enim artisan dolor post-ironic. Pug tote bag Marfa, deserunt pour-over Portland wolf eu odio intelligentsia american apparel ugh ea. Sunt viral et, 3 wolf moon gastropub pug id. Id fashion axe est typewriter, mlkshk Portland art party aute brunch. Sint pork belly Cosby sweater, deep v mumblecore kitsch american apparel. Try-hard direct trade tumblr sint skateboard. Adipisicing bitters excepteur biodiesel, pickled gastropub aute veniam.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample post" /><category term="readability" /><category term="test" /><category term="intro" /><summary type="html">Portland in shoreditch Vice, labore typewriter pariatur hoodie fap sartorial Austin. Pinterest literally occupy Schlitz forage. Odio ad blue bottle vinyl, 90’s narwhal commodo bitters pour-over nostrud. Ugh est hashtag in, fingerstache adipisicing laboris esse Pinterest shabby chic Portland. Shoreditch bicycle rights anim, flexitarian laboris put a bird on it vinyl cupidatat narwhal. Hashtag artisan skateboard, flannel Bushwick nesciunt salvia aute fixie do plaid post-ironic dolor McSweeney’s. Cliche pour-over chambray nulla four loko skateboard sapiente hashtag.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/abstract-6.jpg" /></entry><entry><title type="html">Sample Post</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/sample-post/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Sample Post" /><published>2011-03-10T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2011-03-10T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/sample-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/sample-post/">&lt;p&gt;Below is just about everything you’ll need to style in the theme. Check the source code to see the many embedded elements within paragraphs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;heading-1&quot;&gt;Heading 1&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;heading-2&quot;&gt;Heading 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;heading-3&quot;&gt;Heading 3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;heading-4&quot;&gt;Heading 4&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;heading-5&quot;&gt;Heading 5&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;heading-6&quot;&gt;Heading 6&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;body-text&quot;&gt;Body text&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. &lt;strong&gt;This is strong&lt;/strong&gt;. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;image-right&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://localhost:4000/images/3953273590_704e3899d5_m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Smithsonian Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is emphasized&lt;/em&gt;. Donec faucibus. Nunc iaculis suscipit dui. 53 = 125. Water is H&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;O. Nam sit amet sem. Aliquam libero nisi, imperdiet at, tincidunt nec, gravida vehicula, nisl. The New York Times &lt;cite&gt;(That’s a citation)&lt;/cite&gt;. &lt;u&gt;Underline&lt;/u&gt;. Maecenas ornare tortor. Donec sed tellus eget sapien fringilla nonummy. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HTML and &lt;abbr title=&quot;cascading stylesheets&quot;&gt;CSS&lt;abbr&gt; are our tools. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus. Praesent mattis, massa quis luctus fermentum, turpis mi volutpat justo, eu volutpat enim diam eget metus.&lt;/abbr&gt;&lt;/abbr&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;blockquotes&quot;&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;list-types&quot;&gt;List Types&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ordered-lists&quot;&gt;Ordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item one
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;sub item one&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;sub item two&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;sub item three&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;unordered-lists&quot;&gt;Unordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item one&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item three&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tables&quot;&gt;Tables&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table rules=&quot;groups&quot;&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Header1&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Header2&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;Header3&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell6&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell6&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;tfoot&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Foot1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Foot2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;Foot3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tfoot&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;code-snippets&quot;&gt;Code Snippets&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Syntax highlighting via Rouge&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-css highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;#container&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;float&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;left&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;margin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;-240px&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;nl&quot;&gt;width&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;100%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Non Pygments code example&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&amp;lt;div id=&quot;awesome&quot;&amp;gt;
    &amp;lt;p&amp;gt;This is great isn't it?&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/div&amp;gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;buttons&quot;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make any link standout more when applying the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;.btn&lt;/code&gt; class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-html highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;a&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;href=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;#&quot;&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;na&quot;&gt;class=&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s&quot;&gt;&quot;btn btn-success&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;Success Button&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn&quot;&gt;Primary Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-success&quot;&gt;Success Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-warning&quot;&gt;Warning Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-danger&quot;&gt;Danger Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn btn-info&quot;&gt;Info Button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="sample post" /><summary type="html">Below is just about everything you’ll need to style in the theme. Check the source code to see the many embedded elements within paragraphs.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="http://localhost:4000/images/abstract-3.jpg" /></entry></feed>